Tufts University Television (TUTV) Records UA076
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Television (TUTV) Records
1967 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Television
UA076
22.8 Linear Feet 19 boxes
2 Web sites
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Web crawls and Unprocessed accessions.
Custodial History
Box 2 was sent back to TUTV to look into format migration prior to 2015. It has not been returned.
One box of VHS tapes (Box 19) was removed from the Audio Lab materials series in the Historical Materials collection (UA136.004) and added to this collection by Archives and Research Assistant Tim Walsh in November 2014. It was originally part of accession 2009.024.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains video tapes in various formats for the Tufts University Television station, as well as web crawls of its web presence. The majority of the materials are VHS tapes, though there are a variety of other formats present including Umatic, 3/4 inch, and beta SP. Although TUTV was founded in 1977, this collection contains materials predating its founding that were transferred as part of their records.
Biographical / Historical
Alumnus Andy Liebman founded TUTV in 1977 when, in exchange for taping child development classes and tennis lessons, he received permission to use Tufts' equipment to film TUTV programs. The early years of TUTV consisted of only 10 members. Since its founding, TUTV has grown exponentially in terms of its membership base, resources, scope of activities, and audience.
From 1977 to 1997, TUTV existed primarily as a video club. It had no system for disseminating its programming on a large scale. Instead, TUTV employed a hand-delivery system in which TUTV shuttled copies of its programs back and forth between TUTV's production offices and the Mayer Campus Center. These copies were only available for viewing on VCR in Hotung Cafe or on the televisions in the Mayer Campus Center. As early as the 1980s a cable channel was discussed, but it did not become reality until the mid-1990s when Tufts University's Assistant Director of Telecommunications Marj Minnigh contracted with Campuslink to provide voice, video, and data services to the Tufts residential system, including a closed-circuit cable channel that could be used by Tufts to deliver audiovisual content to their community. Wiring was completed in 1995 and by 1997, TUTV had received nearly $40,000 of funding with $30,000 from the Spaulding Porter Innovative Undergraduate Education Fund and $7,600 from Time Warner Cable. TUTV also received $20,000 from the Office of the Provost. These funds gave TUTV the ability to purchase eight new super VHS cameras and extensive editing equipment. With an updated studio and a cable system, TUTV aired on channel 43 in 1997.
When channel 43 came on-line in 1997, the Tufts administration authorized the Experimental College to oversee its use, with TUTV representatives managing the content creation process. TUTV continued broadcasting on channel 43 and on their website until launching their own channel on YouTube in 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Student life; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations; Student Activities -- Performing Arts; Student life
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2020; UA076.001; 2 Web sites
  Scope and Contents
  Quarterly web crawls of the TUTV websites crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - TUTV, 2015 -- 2020; UA076.001.00001; Tufts University Television
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research.
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.
  - TUTV - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA076.001.00002; Tufts University Television
    Frequency: quarterly crawl. (Inactive)
- Audiovisual materials, UA076.002
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  This series consists of VHS, U-matic, and helical scan videotapes. Access to these materials may be limited depending on availability of appropriate playback equipment. Please contact the archives for details.
  This series is open for research.
  Arrangement
  This series maintains its received arrangement.
  This series contains material originally aired on TUTV, or otherwise transferred as part of their records. The series consists mainly of VHS videotapes but also includes U-matic and helical scan videotapes.
  - Random jazz band, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Raw footage Oliver Platt with Mr. Tim (Bird), circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - 111, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - 440 Sailing, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Dec 17 NY Tel Reel10, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - 112, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - 53, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - 101, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - The lover, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Common principles course 40265 Zener Diodes module 3.1, Unit2, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Joe the rider sound only prod. in prog., circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Sailing coach interview, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Hunter module meeting John Felsman continued, 1973-11-12; UA076.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Don Olenick contracting session winter module, 1974-03-28; UA076.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - College within staff meeting, 1973-11-01; UA076.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - College within staff discussion, 1973-11-08; UA076.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Jeff Milliken contracting session Orenstein module, 1974-04-02; UA076.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Mort Walker at the college within and Minardi module meeting, 1973-11-13 -- 1973-11-27; UA076.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Mort Walker at the college within, 1973-11-13; UA076.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Staff meeting continued and Orenstien module office hours Andrea Leis, 1973-11-01 -- 1973-11-06; UA076.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Staff discussion continued and Hunter module meeting John Felsman, 1973-11-08 -- 1973-11-12; UA076.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Winter module meeting Owen Morrison presentation, 1973-12-04; UA076.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Mort Walker at the college within continued, 1973-11-13; UA076.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Orenstien module office hours Anrea Leis continued, 1973-11-06; UA076.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Winter module meeting Owen Morrison presentation continued, 1973-12-04; UA076.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Untitled, circa 1960s -- 1970s; UA076.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - 46 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - 47 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - 23 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - 41 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - 42 TUTV Thighs Like Mighty Redwoods master Talking With master, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - 39 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - 45 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - 49 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - 27 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - 38 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - 18 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - 48 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - 28 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - 7 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - 10 TUTV raw footage from an early promo, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - 11 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - 22 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Safety gear respirators, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Untitled, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.004.00001 (Box 3)
  - 61 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - 1, circa 1960s -- 1970s; UA076.002.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Is Humor Dangerous? WGBH, 1972-07-26; UA076.002.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - 5, circa 1960s -- 1970s; UA076.002.004.00005; Starting to unspool (Box 4)
  - John Anderson Cohen auditorium, 1980-02-01; UA076.002.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Common principles course 40265 magnetic amplifiers, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - A lecture on logo 25, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Tim footage, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Campus footage 41, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Graduation? Commencement? 39, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - WCVB TV news 31, 1984-02-06; UA076.002.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Boycott 38, 1985-09-19; UA076.002.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Apple II video, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - A tribute to the class of 1993 tape 73, circa 1990s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Premiere party handheld camera tape 149, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - The legacy II special edit tape 164, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Raw footage tape 92, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - For the daily on campus sports doc classic TUTV tape 91, 1998-11-03 -- 1998-11-16; UA076.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Newer "On the Hills" no intro or credit tape 90, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - TUTV tape library 153, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - TUTV tape library 152, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Blue group "slacker" tape 147, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Blue group tape 143, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - TUTV tape library 155, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - TUTV tape library 156, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Return to exile Gutierrez, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - On campus episode 202 tape 159, 1998-04-08; UA076.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - SOC the legacy tape 163, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Dialogue tape 144, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Red green blue documentaries and TV tape 146, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Tape 88, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Beauty and the Beast tape 87, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Tape 124, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Tape 125, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - The Air on the Hill tape 110, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Tape 111, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Tape 82, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Tape 122, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Tape 123, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - SOC bounce on campus tape 129, 1999-03-09; UA076.002.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Legacy II act II almost ivy tape 128, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - The legacy act I tape 127, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Tape 126, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Library footage Hillel Hanukah display, 1998-12-01; UA076.002.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Tuftsablanca, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - 17 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Applause for a cause tape 99, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Tape 83, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Talking with tape 84, 1990; UA076.002.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Tape 121, 1997-11-18; UA076.002.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Afro-Cuban jazz master Cohen Aud., 2000-02-04; UA076.002.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - On campus live 102, 1999-11-11; UA076.002.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Learning AB roll editing with Howard, 1997-11-09; UA076.002.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Untitled, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00041 (Box 5)
  - S29 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00042 (Box 5)
  - S15 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00043 (Box 5)
  - S34 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00044 (Box 5)
  - S22 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00045 (Box 5)
  - UPM training 2, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00046 (Box 5)
  - UPM training 1, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00047 (Box 5)
  - Tape 130, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.005.00048 (Box 5)
  - 51 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - 57 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - S72 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - 56 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - 50 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - 54 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - 29 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Untitled, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - 20 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - 30 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - 21 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - 19 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - 31 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - 32 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - 33 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - 35 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - 25 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - 26 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - 37 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - 62 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - 59 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - 55 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - 53 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - I1, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - B TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - 1 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - 2 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - 3 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - 4 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - 5 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - 6 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Common principles course 40265 module 9.5 unit 6, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Part II on line certification verification post processor, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Federal government pension plan, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Part V on line certification radar enhancements, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Part III on line certification quatradisk, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Part VI on line certification NAS enhancements, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - Tape 2, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Part I on line certification introduction, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - 35 roommate game, 1979-10-25; UA076.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Part VIII on line certification RPAT, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Common principles course 40265 resonant line module 9.1 unit 13, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Paradyne training tape 2, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Part IV on line certification adaptation, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Part VII on line certification radar performance monitor, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Tape 18 roommate game II, 1979-11-15; UA076.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Tape 9 random title screens, 1986; UA076.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Tufts today auditions, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - Tape 4 Tufts vs Williams, 1981-10-24; UA076.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Tape 3, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - TUTV hour on SCAT tape 140, 1999-03-10; UA076.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Tape 134, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Tape 139 red group TV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Tape 138 TUTV on SCAT hour, 1999-02-24; UA076.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Tape 141, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Tape 142 the air on the hill, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Tape 167 Margaret Thatcher, 1997-09-24; UA076.002.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Tape 169 sportsdoc 102 master, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Tape 154 full court press, 1997 -- 1998; UA076.002.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Tape 161, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Tape 158 Hollywood, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Tape 162 on campus episode 103, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Tape 13 blind date, 1979-02-04; UA076.002.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Tape 76 roommate game 2, 1981-11-11; UA076.002.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Tape 63, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Tape 51, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - Tape 137 Dave tape, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Tape 136 Vanessa's house and TUTV balcony, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Tape 74, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Tape 66 HJW 3, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Tape 69 campus center opening, 1985-02-01; UA076.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Tape 135 86.06 through 86.08, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Tape 73 OT school scene footage, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Tape 75 first workshop talk show apple jam, 1986-01; UA076.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Tape 45, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Tape 80, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Tape 42 Tracks Inn trailer, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Tape 48 dorm feud edited master, 1985-10; UA076.002.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Tape 49, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Tape 47, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Tape 46 Randi Botrick, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Tape 123, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Tape 125 Robin Masheb AIDS controversy raw footage, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Tape 77, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Tape 43, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Tape 90 Magnifique episode 1, 1986-03-30; UA076.002.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Tape 89 interview Stephanie Bavaro pres BSOT club, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Tape 126 Robin Masheb AIDS controversy raw footage, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Tape 88, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Tape 131 terrorism symposium, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Tape 64 Tim footage, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Tape 86 campus news master, 1986-02-28; UA076.002.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Tape 99, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Tape 138, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Tape 63 dorm feud, 1985-10; UA076.002.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Tape 98 christening the car, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Tape 96 crime and punishment, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Tape 144 mod squad, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Tape 145 mod squad, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Tape 134 look at me raw 2, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - Tape 142, 1979-12; UA076.002.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - Tape 66 HJW 1, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - Tape 133 look at me raw 1, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - Tape 14, 1999-01-14; UA076.002.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Children of Heaven, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Tape 152 interviews tape 4, 1981-01-13; UA076.002.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Tape 119, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - Tape 124 TCB family feud tape 2, 1985-10-17; UA076.002.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - Tape 19, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - Tape 127 Robin Masheb AIDs controversy raw footage, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - Tape 129, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - Tape 130, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.011.00009 (Box 11)
    Includes text description of the contents of this tape and UA076.002.011.00008 (the previous item).
  - Playing by heart, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - Tape 85, 1986-02-10; UA076.002.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - Tape 44 apocalypse 1637, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - Tape 23 S48 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - Tape 25 S52 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - Tape 24 S49 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - Tape 29 S63 TUTV, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - Tape 28 S60 slices episode, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - Tape 44 S73, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - Tape 153, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Tape 118, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.012.00002 (Box 12)
  - Tape 78 eligibility blues, Tufts sit in and boycott, 1985-10-17; UA076.002.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Tape 68 campus feud, 1985; UA076.002.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Tape 32 Tufts today A. House, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.012.00005 (Box 12)
  - Tape 67 blind date 3, 1982-02-11; UA076.002.012.00006 (Box 12)
  - Tape 120, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.012.00007 (Box 12)
  - Tape 56 community circle master edit, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.012.00008 (Box 12)
  - Tape 41 WMFO edited master, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.012.00009 (Box 12)
  - Tape 59 distinguished lecture series Dr. Purcell, 1978-12-08; UA076.002.012.00010 (Box 12)
  - Tape 30 newsviews 1 presidential race, 1980-02-22; UA076.002.012.00011 (Box 12)
  - Tape 72 Randy tape, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.012.00012 (Box 12)
  - Tape 93 Sarabande dance concert, 1986-03-11; UA076.002.013.00001 (Box 13)
  - Untitled, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00002 (Box 13)
  - Tape 91 freedom music concert, 1986-03-29; UA076.002.013.00003 (Box 13)
  - Tape 148 crew interview, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00004 (Box 13)
  - Tape 57 "On the Town", circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00005 (Box 13)
  - Tape 54 rough video titles, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00006 (Box 13)
  - Tape 83 Bruce Springsteen 103 WSHE special, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00007 (Box 13)
  - Tape 92 freedom music concert, 1986-03-29; UA076.002.013.00008 (Box 13)
  - Tape 132 terrorism symposium, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00009 (Box 13)
  - Tape 160, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00010 (Box 13)
  - Tape 65, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00011 (Box 13)
  - Tape 117, circa 1970s -- 1980s; UA076.002.013.00012 (Box 13)
  - Tape 115 news program, Magnifique soap opera, 1986; UA076.002.013.00013 (Box 13)
  - S41 tape 19, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00001 (Box 14)
  - Tape 20, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00002 (Box 14)
  - Tape 21, circa 1970s -- 2000s; UA076.002.014.00003 (Box 14)